{
    "id": "ae8457def7144688b121a60fed2bea4e",
    "title": "English Vocabulary Exercise",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "Helping that family was a very ………………………… thing to do.",
            "description": "Humane means the quality of being kind towards others.",
            "answers": [
                "human",
                "humane"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "We all belong to the ……………………………… race.",
            "description": "Human race means mankind.",
            "answers": [
                "humane",
                "human"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "The team’s …………………………… is on the rise.",
            "description": "Morale is the level of confidence.",
            "answers": [
                "morale",
                "moral"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "He was an honest, ………………………………. man.",
            "description": "Moral is the principle of right and wrong.",
            "answers": [
                "moral",
                "morale"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "A warm smile …………………………. up her face.",
            "description": "Either lighted or lit is possible here. ",
            "answers": [
                "lighted",
                "lited",
                "lit"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        },
        {
            "question": "The children ……………………………. from the train.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "lighted",
                "alighted"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "I call my mother …………………………………",
            "description": "Every day means daily.",
            "answers": [
                "every day",
                "everyday"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "……………………………… chores like cooking and cleaning consume much of my time.",
            "description": "Everyday means day to day.",
            "answers": [
                "Everyday",
                "Every day"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "Tell me the amount in ………………………. figures.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "round",
                "around"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "No country can be overly dependent on foreign ……………………………….",
            "description": "Aid means assistance.",
            "answers": [
                "aid",
                "aide"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "I couldn’t meet the President but I did talk to his …………………………….",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "aid",
                "aide"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "This medicine is ……………………………… at alleviating the pain.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "effective",
                "efficient"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        }
    ]
}